时间轴/翻译/压制：旋火
视频来源：youtu.be/r4PJ-ss9L5s
原视频发布日期：20191202
原作者名：johnkrausphotos
VA250发射发生在2019年11月26日
载荷是Inmarsat-5 F5，TIBA-1
[Music]
奥兰多在佛罗里达州
奥兰多
新泽西州纽瓦克国际机场
纽瓦克
*飞去法国巴黎*
[Music]
巴黎
*飞去法属圭亚那卡宴*
[Music]
法属圭亚那
Wow, amazing.
喔 令人惊讶
We are very close to the rocket where will be.
我们离火箭发射时的位置很近
So we are using a weight to make sure this don't lie.
所以我们使用重物来确保三脚架不会翻倒
You will be more scary when you go to this.
如果用这个会更吓人
I think the weight might need to be I think the weight is too forward right now?
我觉得现在这个重物可能放得太靠前了
So may be bring it away. Instead of resting on the front.
所以可能还是拿开 拿到后面好些
You are pointing at what you think the rocket will be.
你要指向你觉得火箭以后会在的地方
我们又去了发射台好几次，进行了额外的配置和安全检查……
[Music]
右边这位是Trevor Mahlmann
All right, we are 10 minutes out from VA250 Ariane 5.
我们离阿丽亚娜5的VA250发射还差10分钟了
星期五：第一次发射尝试
And fully on the ground here setting up.
都安排上了
For just over 5 kilometers from the launch pad which is somewhere that way.
我们离发射台大概5km远
And yeah I'm nervous and that's all.
我现在比较紧张 就这些
Let's do it.
来吧
此次发射原定于11月22日，因地面设备问题推迟
There you see the red in the hold in the countdown
倒数停下来 (背景是)红色的
which you didn't see before.
和之前看到的不一样
That's all we know. We have a hold in the countdown.
我们现在知道的就是这些 倒数停下了
The launcher and the satellites of course have been placed in safe configuration.
当然 火箭和卫星现在处于安全配置中
The launcher's postponed.
发射延后了
and that's all we know for now.
现在只知道这些
Stephan Israel是阿丽亚娜空间公司的CEO
but we're waiting for word from Stephan Israel who will tell us more.
我们会等待Stephan Israel的更多消息
So we were in the final operations
那么我们之前是在最终操作阶段了
and we have faced an issue on ground means
我们遇到了地面设备的问题
and consequently Ariane Space has decided decided to stop the final operations for today.
所以阿丽亚娜空间决定停止今天最终阶段的操作
For sure launcher and spacecraft are in the self mode.
当然 火箭和航天器都处在自动(控制)状态
And we are now targeting new launch window tomorrow.
我们现在为明早的发射窗口作准备
and we will keep you posted for sure.
并且我们会时常公布情况
Thank you very much thank you.
非常感谢大家
So we need to be a little more patient but it will be ok thank you.
我们只需要一点耐心 就没问题了 谢谢大家
接下来几天外面下雨了。我们的相机留在了发射台(那边)，被水泡着。
这是晚上下雨时的音频，雨声大到把我们都吵醒了！
[Music]
我们利用延迟的这几天出去探索了一番……顺便补补觉。
没人能想到要等这么多次发射尝试，为了住最后四晚上，我们不得不换了家酒店……
标牌上的字：欢迎来到库鲁
星期二：我们最后一次尝试看发射
Can we go? Yes*n
我们可以开始了吗？好*n
发射后的聚会！
这次发射完美！在聚会之后，第二天早上需要回收剩下的前方远程相机了。
You got anything, John?
John 你拍到什么了吗
Hold on.
等下
Look.
看
Fantastique.
好极了
It's wet but it's fired.
虽然被水泡了 但还是拍下来了
It will be something.
会拍下来些东西的
Just the lens is wet.
只有镜头是湿的
But it worked.
但还是工作了
Here we go.
来吧
Did you get anything?
你拍到了什么吗
You get it?
你拍到了吗
Yeah, did you?
我拍到了 你呢
You get it?
你拍到了？
Got it.
拍到了
Bravo guys.
干得漂亮 兄弟们
Let's go.
我们走吧
[Music]
特别感谢欧空局和阿丽亚娜集团给予的这次机会！
感谢Julio Aprea和Julien Watelet的指导和款待，
还有你们为此视频提供的素材。
想看到更多我的航天摄影可以上我的网站：
johnkrausphotos.com
任何其他地方：
@johnkrausphotos
考虑在Patreon上支持我：
patreon.com/johnkrausphotos